

Andrey V Web Developer Django

LANGUAGES

English - B1

WHO AM I?

Programming languages: Python, CSS, HTML Databases: MySQL. PostgreSQL, QSLAlchemy Frameworks: Django, Django Rest Framework(DRF), Wegtail, Experience in leadership positions in projects in various fields. Successful start-up of projects from scratch and implementation of the set goals. Formation of tasks for the team and control of the stages of their implementation. Practice and experience in finance and financial planning, partly in the tax code, negotiating at a high level. Purpose: completely re-profiled in the field of IT technologies, took a courses in the direction of "data science" and backend developer in Python I am interested in the financial sphere, modern technologies, I like to travel. I am fond of: motorcycle travel, surfing, team sports. I try to keep my mind and body in balance and develop every day.

SKILLS

Python	Django	Django Rest Framework(DRF)				ram API	telebot	Docker	PostgreSQL
MySQL	SQLAlche	SQLAlchemy/Alembic		SQL CSS		HTML Machine learning			

EDUCATION

2000 — 2005 Ural State Technical University

Department of Graphic Design bachelor's diplomas

2020 — 2021 Netology school online

education: Data scince language: Python libraries: Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib & Seaborn, Scikit-learn, Plotly

EXPERIENCE

2022 — 2022 SMS send REST API

Urbamatica

Mission: Design and develop a service that, according to the given rules, launches a mailing list according to a list of clients.

Python Django Django Rest Framework(DRF)

2022 - 2022

Parser

Urbamatica

Mission: Parsing json Creating a nested dictionary for the selected Nick Using ORM SQLAlchemy add data to the database

Python

SQLAlchemy/Alembic

2022 - 2022

My blog

Urbamatica

Mission: Development of a personal website with and put on the web

Python

Django Docker

PostgreSQL

css

HTML

Bootstrap

2022 - 2022

Analysis of employee productivity and the likelihood of dismissal

Netology

Name project: HR Varganov_AO Mission: 1) Calculate basic statistics for variables (mean, median, mode, min / max, mean deviation). 2) Calculate and visualize the correlation matrix for quantitative variables. identify the two most correlated and two least correlated variables. 3) Calculate how many employees work in each department. 4) Show employee distribution by salary. 5) Show the distribution of employees by salary in each department separately. 6) Test the hypothesis that high-paid employees spend more time at work than low-paid employees. 7) Calculate the following indicators among employees who quit and did not quit (separately): ● share of employees with an increase over the last 5 years ● average degree of satisfaction ● average number of projects 8) Divide data into test and training samples. Build an LDA model that predicts whether an employee quits based on available factors (other than department and salary). Assess the quality of the model on the test sample. Technologies used: sklearn, matplotlib, numpy, pandas, scipy, seaborn, pylab, scipy

Python

Machine learning

2022 - 2022

Analysis of sales of the game platform and genre in the world Netology

Name project: Game Platform Mission: determine the top selling platform in different countries Mission: determine the most popular game genre by country Technologies used: matplotlib, numpy, pandas, seaborn

Python

2021 — 2021 (ML) Predict an employee's income level

Netology

Name project: HW_logis_regres_and_SVM Mission: Predict an employee's income level Technologies used: SVM, sklearn, matplotlib, pandas

Python

Machine learning

2021 - 2021 (ML) Search for toxic comments

Netology

Name project: Toxic_words Target: Mission: Train the model for recognizing coarse comments, setting the precision and recall metrics. Error level no more than 5% Technologies used: sklearn, sklearn.pipeline, sklearn.linear_model, sklearn.feature_extraction.text, sklearn.metrics, pandas, numpy, nltk, nltk.corpus, nltk.stem, nltk.tokenize, string

Python

Machine learning

2021 — 2021 **Loan approval**

Netology

Name project: Loan approved Mission: Identify clients who will repay the Ioan Technologies used: sklearn, matplotlib, numpy, pandas, scipy, seaborn

Python

2021 — 2021 Speech recognition

Netology

Name project: Recognize_sound _1. Mission: Recognize sound and launching the application git hub using voice. Technology: speech_recognition

Python

2022 — 2022 **Web scraping**

Urbamatica

Mission: A customer from USA needed scalping of a third-party site Description of tasks: Authorization in website Scraping of shipping data Test Solving the problem: Authorization in to website using Selenium and WebDriver. Scraping the site using Python, the data was received and converted into a dictionary

Python | Selenium